Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series
are fictional and created
for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
I know that you were hurt when I left you.
I had no choice.
Don’t be sad, Chan.
I want to be by your side
and take care of you for a long time.
If you kiss me
and you don’t feel that excitement,
I will let you go.
Key.
Key, wait.
Every time I kiss you.
My heart is always beating fast.
It happens only with you.
We met before?
Yes.
When I was 15.
I’m sorry.
I don’t remember it.
It’s okay.
It happened ten years ago.
It’s not surprising that you forgot it.
But you remember me.
You’ve never forgotten me.
You can be mad at me.
I forgot something this important.
I deserve it.
Fine.
I admit that I’m a little upset about it.
But I’m more upset
when I saw you kiss another woman.
I’m sorry.
Your apology is not enough.
What do I need to do?
So you will stop being mad at me.
There’s actually a way.
Tonight.
I’ll be the only one who can kiss you.
You can’t kiss me
without my permission.
Is this your way of getting back at me?
Will you agree to it?
Fine.
From now on,
I’ll let you have your way.
Then I won’t hold back.
I have something important to tell you.
I want to cancel our deal.
I don’t want you…
to be my sugar baby anymore.
Key.
Will you be my girlfriend?
Yes.
I have wanted to be your girlfriend
for a long time.
So you are now my girlfriend.
Hey.
Don’t forget.
You can’t kiss me
without my permission.
Fine.
♪ Just hold my gaze a little longer ♪
♪ Move your heart a little closer ♪
♪ Let’s take the meaning of love
a little further ♪
♪ What we have doesn't end tonight ♪
Don’t play dumb.
I can’t help it. I’m used to it.
♪ I’ll make you love me,
make you remember ♪
♪ I’ll keep repeating till you surrender ♪
♪ With every touch, remember only me ♪
♪ I’ll hold you close in everything I do ♪
♪ Make it sink in, make you remember too ♪
That’s cheating.
Let’s go back to my room.
As we have agreed.
Tonight,
I’m the only one who can kiss you.
You can’t kiss me
without my permission.
Will you be my girlfriend?
Yes.
Miss Chan.
Mr. Phu wants to see you.
Send him in.
Please come in.
Thank you.
Chan.
Morning, Phu.
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
Why?
No.
This is not normal.
You said ‘Good morning’ to me.
You also smile.
You barely smile to anyone.
From now on, I’ll smile more often.
You are in such a good mood.
Because Jay
checked out of the hotel, right?
Jay told you that?
Yes.
She also asked me to tell you
that she would keep her word.
That’s all?
Yes.
Right, the money that I owed Jay.
I almost paid it all back.
I got money from my dad.
You don’t need to worry
that Jay will ask me to do something.
I will cut ties with her.
Thank you, Phu.
Thank me?
I should be the one who thanks you
for not ending our friendship.
If I cut you off,
I would have no friends left.
I still feel guilty anyway.
I’m sorry, Chan.
Forget it.
It’s in the past now.
But you need to promise me.
From now on, if you have a problem,
you need to tell me.
Don’t be afraid to ask for my help.
Get it?
Yes.
I promise.
Phu.
You told me you have a friend
who is a tattoo artist, right?
He did tattoos for many celebrities.
Yes.
Why?
Is it heavy? Let me help you.
I won’t come to meet you
before our performance tomorrow.
I’ll send you the setlist.
I’ll go meet you at the Crescent.
Our frontman flakes on us again.
I have a matter to tend to.
What matter?
A matter of the heart?
I knew it.
Key is in such a good mood today.
She only sang love songs today.
When we were going to play a sad song,
she told us to play other songs.
You’re right.
A few days ago,
you were moping around like a sad puppy.
What’s going on?
Spill it.
Nothing is going on.
I just…
I…
I have a girlfriend.
Damn!
Why are you that surprised?
I didn’t mishear it, right?
I can’t believe it.
Key has stopped flirting around.
Yeah.
Didn’t you say you didn’t want
to be in a relationship?
I said that because
I’ve been waiting for her.
All my life,
I will be committed only to her.
Her? Who is she?
Let me see her picture.
-Come on. Let us see it.
-Let us see it.
-Grab her.
-No.
-Come on. Let us see her picture.
-Show it to us.
-No.
We won’t tell anyone.
No.
What are you doing here?
I came to pick you up.
You don’t work today, do you?
Yes.
We just finished our practice.
We’re about to go home.
Miss Chan, you and Key…
We are dating.
They are dating.
You are dating?
Come on.
Let’s go home, sweetie.
I’ll help you carry it.
Yes.
Honey.
Let’s go.
Are you leaving?
Get in.
She suddenly acts all needy.
What’s the occasion?
It…
It’s a very special occasion.
Our anniversary?
I don’t think so.
Did something good happen to you?
Let’s say it’s something
you’d never expect.
So…
What do I need to do for you to tell me?
Do you really want to know it?
Yes.
Can you help me take my jacket off?
You are acting strange today.
So?
Can you tell me now?
Don’t you notice anything?
Any changes in me?
You got a tattoo?
Keep your voice down.
You’re startling others.
Did you get the treble clef tattoo for me?
Yes.
This time,
I will remember you.
To tell you the truth,
the tattoo has another meaning.
When we write a song,
the first thing we write
is the treble clef.
It’s the beginning of everything.
Just like you.
You are a new beginning for me.
Because of you,
I want to start singing again.
The tattoo,
are you sure about it?
Why?
You also have a tattoo.
I think this tattoo looks great.
Won’t your family be against it?
One more thing.
It might not look good
for an executive like you.
Managing the business,
I use my brain.
It has nothing to do with my tattoo.
About my family,
I don’t think
they will have a problem with it.
I’m an adult.
My body, my choice.
No one will judge me
because of the tattoo.
Thank you for doing this for me.
From now on,
I will do everything only for you.
You are crazy in love.
I like this side of you.
This is the first time
that I’m late to work.
You are only a few minutes late.
I always come to work early.
But you can’t blame me.
You were the one who wouldn’t go to sleep.
How could I go to sleep
when you wore that nightgown?
Did you like it?
Yes.
Then stop complaining.
But you need to stop
distracting me from work.
Do you get it, stubborn kid?
I got it.
You should go to work.
I’ll hang around to wait for you.
Let’s have lunch together.
Lunch?
Yes.
I know a restaurant
serving delicious food.
It also has a nice atmosphere.
Can I have a rain check?
I have a meeting today.
What about dinner?
I don’t know when I will get off work.
But I know.
How?
When I go to see you,
it’s time for you to get off work.
Do your best at work.
I’ve got to go.
Wait.
-Bye.
-See you.
I’m afraid that, about the increased budget
for personnel training,
Madam Chanya will not agree.
Our hotel receives high ratings
for staff services.
I think it’s reasonable to increase
the budget for training new staff.
About my mom,
I’ll take care of it.
What about the room rate increase?
Due to the rising costs
and higher living expenses,
I think we need to consider
increasing the room rate.
About that, I don’t want to do it now.
I think we should launch a campaign
to attract customers.
Our cost is indeed rising.
But we can make profits from
the high quality of our rooms and services.
But I still think it’s necessary
to increase the room rate.
All our costs have gone up.
Miss Chan, Miss Key is waiting to see you.
Let’s wrap up the meeting here.
But we haven’t reached a conclusion yet.
We can discuss it tomorrow.
We’ve had this meeting for five hours.
Many of you started to feel tired,
didn’t you?
But we haven’t reached a conclusion yet.
That’s right.
Are you hungry?
My stomach is growling.
Let’s go find Simba.
Simba.
Jay.
You’re finally home.
I thought you would be alone.
I didn’t think that
you two would be attached at the hip.
Can you stop coming to my condo?
To be honest, what you did is illegal.
Now we are not together.
This suddenly became illegal.
Even if you were still together,
you shouldn’t come into
her room like this.
I’m just used to it.
I could come in here
since we were in school.
What do you want?
I thought this was your personal space.
So I came here to talk to you in private.
I didn’t think anyone else would be here.
Let’s talk when we are alone.
This place is no longer
Chan’s personal space.
Right now,
it has become a personal space
for her and me.
If you want to talk to Chan,
you can do it now.
Chan and I,
we have no secrets from each other.
But if you don’t want to talk,
you should leave.
Okay.
I’ll leave.
You got a tattoo?
Yes.
It’s pretty.
I like it.
Here is your keycard.
Goodbye.
It’s really over.
From now on,
you don’t need to worry anymore.
You are the only one I love.
I won’t hesitate anymore.
I won’t hurt you again.
You got a tattoo?
Yes.
Jay looks terrible right now.
What do you want me to do?
It’s obvious that she’s trying
to get my attention.
Yes, I know.
For the sake of our friendship,
I want you to talk to her.
I never thought that a girl like Jay
could fall apart like this.
What can I say to her?
She won’t listen to me anyway.
She will listen to you.
You are the only person in this world
that she listens to.
Jay and I,
we are over.
You refuse to talk to her
because you’re afraid
that it will upset your girlfriend?
Yes.
I hurt her too many times.
Right now, she is the only one
I care about.
About Jay, we just need to let her
deal with it on her own.
I can’t help her.
Here is your coffee.
Can I have a cup of warm water?
Sure.
Thank you.
What are you doing here?
We seem to…
have similar tastes.
If you’re here to pick a fight,
I’ll leave.
I’m not talking about Chan.
Are you going to rub it in my face?
You think I’m that kind of person?
Can’t we be friends?
or sisters?
Are you serious?
Do you really think we can?
If the situation were reversed,
if Chan and I got back together,
would you still want to be
my friend or sister?
I probably couldn’t do it.
Hey.
I hate when people feel bad for me.
My life isn’t that bad.
You are acting as if you care about me.
Is it because Chan refused to see me?
Let me tell you something.
Chan is right that she refused to see me.
Even if she came to talk to me,
to take care of me,
it would make things worse for me.
She knows me well.
What you are doing right now,
do you think you are an angel?
You must feel good to act like a saint.
I never thought I was an angel.
I came here
because I thought…
we once really hit it off.
Even though it was only a short time.
If you don’t want to be my friend,
I get it.
Even if I move on from Chan,
you and I,
we can never be friends.
Just so you know.
Your relationship with Chan,
it will not be easy.
Be careful.
(Jay.)
Are you getting drunk again?
It’s my life,
not your business, Auntie.
I can’t stand it anymore.
If someone finds out
that you are getting drunk every night,
what would I do?
(I don’t f*cking care.)
Don’t call me again.
You know?!
Jay.
You are acting out of control.
Sorry.
It’s okay.
I’m sorry.
You’re finally up.
Are you sober now?
You…
You are confused about who I am
and how you ended up here, right?
Last night,
you and I…
Did we sleep together?
Calm down, Miss.
I don’t like sleeping with a drunk woman,
especially a woman who threw up
and passed out on the street.
Hey.
Take your money back.
Do you hear me?
Here. I put it back.
Can you slap me?
What?
Please.
Can you slap me?
I’m begging you.
I want to wake up. Please slap me.
Can you slap me on the face?
What’s wrong with you?
-Slap me. I want to wake up.
-No, let me go.
I want to wake up. Please slap me.
Slap me. Slap me now.
So?
Did you wake up now?
Did it hurt enough?
What the heck is this?
Hey.
Hey, stop it.
You threw up and passed out.
So I had to take you back here.
I didn’t know where you live.
You didn’t have your phone with you.
I’m sorry for causing you trouble.
I’ll pay you back for wasting your time.
Can’t you talk about
something else besides money?
I want to make it up to you.
I guess your life is always
revolving around money and benefits.
You don’t need to pay me back.
You just need to…
leave my room.
-Are you telling me to get out?
-You are up.
There’s no need to stay here any longer.
Please leave.
What about this shirt?
It belongs to someone I was talking to.
But we are no longer talking.
I don’t want it back.
You can keep it.
I just leave?
-My under…
-It’s in the bathroom.
(Let me tell you something.)
Your relationship with Chan,
it will not be easy.
Be careful.
What are you doing?
Can I play this piano?
Sure.
But you need to tell me first.
Is something bothering you?
Yesterday,
I went to see Jay.
She snapped at you, didn’t she?
You really know her well.
Yes.
We’ve been friends since we were young.
But I have no feelings for her now.
I know you love me,
and you have no feelings for her.
Since you know that,
what’s the problem?
Do you think we can make it work?
Yes.
No matter what problem arises,
I will make this relationship work.
I want to be with you like this
until we grow old.
Until your hair turns grey,
you need to wear dentures,
and you always look for your glasses.
Do you like that?
You really painted a picture.
Shall we play it together?
Sun is probably back.
I’ll check the door.
What’s up, Sun?
Key, wait.
Mom.
How could you do this?
Why did you get a tattoo?
Do you think this is appropriate?
It’s just a tattoo.
It doesn’t define my worth, Mom.
Chan.
Excuse me.
Even though she’s your daughter,
you shouldn’t use violence with her.
Who do you think you are?
Do you want to show off
that you’re my daughter’s sugar baby?
If my mom does this again,
you need to tell me immediately.
I like it when you protect me.
I think Key is not a good match
for my daughter.
She deserves someone better.
What do you want me to do?
Do you think
you are different from your mom?
Your mom was sick.
How can I be sure
that you won’t have the same illness?
She is dead because of you.
If you won’t stop talking badly to her,
I’ll have to protect her.